{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 8?",
      "options": [
        14,
        7,
        20,
        13
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 7?",
      "options": [
        14,
        18,
        10,
        15
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 7?",
      "options": [
        21,
        7,
        14,
        16
      ],
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 9?",
      "options": [
        25,
        12,
        7,
        15
      ],
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 6?",
      "options": [
        4,
        5,
        11,
        14
      ],
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 9?",
      "options": [
        18,
        7,
        8,
        15
      ],
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 8?",
      "options": [
        17,
        21,
        20,
        7
      ],
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 6?",
      "options": [
        5,
        13,
        4,
        12
      ],
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 6?",
      "options": [
        14,
        9,
        15,
        4
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 5?",
      "options": [
        19,
        4,
        6,
        10
      ],
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 5?",
      "options": [
        13,
        15,
        14,
        4
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 8?",
      "options": [
        7,
        13,
        17,
        8
      ],
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 5?",
      "options": [
        9,
        5,
        1,
        11
      ],
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 5?",
      "options": [
        19,
        14,
        21,
        13
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 6?",
      "options": [
        4,
        18,
        19,
        11
      ],
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 8?",
      "options": [
        22,
        13,
        16,
        10
      ],
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 5?",
      "options": [
        12,
        13,
        15,
        11
      ],
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 9?",
      "options": [
        16,
        14,
        8,
        6
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 8?",
      "options": [
        17,
        11,
        25,
        20
      ],
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 7?",
      "options": [
        11,
        18,
        6,
        14
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 8?",
      "options": [
        17,
        18,
        5,
        15
      ],
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 6?",
      "options": [
        15,
        18,
        10,
        14
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 5?",
      "options": [
        12,
        7,
        5,
        10
      ],
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 5?",
      "options": [
        13,
        8,
        17,
        15
      ],
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 6?",
      "options": [
        16,
        18,
        12,
        9
      ],
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 6?",
      "options": [
        20,
        25,
        15,
        7
      ],
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 7?",
      "options": [
        5,
        24,
        15,
        19
      ],
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 6?",
      "options": [
        20,
        13,
        23,
        12
      ],
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 5?",
      "options": [
        11,
        3,
        16,
        8
      ],
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 7?",
      "options": [
        5,
        12,
        3,
        10
      ],
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 8?",
      "options": [
        21,
        23,
        17,
        15
      ],
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 8?",
      "options": [
        13,
        14,
        15,
        10
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 7?",
      "options": [
        11,
        13,
        20,
        12
      ],
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 9?",
      "options": [
        19,
        16,
        8,
        11
      ],
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 9?",
      "options": [
        23,
        17,
        25,
        27
      ],
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 9?",
      "options": [
        24,
        17,
        21,
        14
      ],
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 9?",
      "options": [
        21,
        18,
        16,
        17
      ],
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 7?",
      "options": [
        23,
        17,
        8,
        15
      ],
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 8?",
      "options": [
        26,
        17,
        16,
        21
      ],
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 5?",
      "options": [
        15,
        20,
        10,
        16
      ],
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 6 + 7?",
      "options": [
        13,
        7,
        18,
        4
      ],
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 6?",
      "options": [
        20,
        15,
        5,
        17
      ],
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 9?",
      "options": [
        18,
        19,
        20,
        8
      ],
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 7?",
      "options": [
        14,
        15,
        16,
        26
      ],
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 9?",
      "options": [
        16,
        9,
        19,
        12
      ],
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 8 + 5?",
      "options": [
        13,
        16,
        8,
        15
      ],
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 7?",
      "options": [
        8,
        12,
        6,
        18
      ],
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 9 + 9?",
      "options": [
        20,
        18,
        21,
        23
      ],
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 5 + 8?",
      "options": [
        13,
        17,
        21,
        9
      ],
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "Level 2: What is 7 + 6?",
      "options": [
        13,
        10,
        23,
        5
      ],
      "answer": 13
    }
  ]
}